Preliminary Guide to the Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records, 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1956-1992
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence with AIS/DC Dance COS and DMS (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, Jan. 1-June 30, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, NEA, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, Chron File, Jan 1- June 30, 1977 (Box 24)
  - AIS Chronological File, Corres, July 1-Dec. 30, 1977 (Box 24)
  - AIS/Dance Component Correspondence, Jan 1-June 30, 1978 (Box 24)
  - AIS Correspondence (Chron), July 1- Aug. 31, 1978 (Box 24)
  - AIS Chronological File, Corres, Sept 1- Dec. 31, 1978 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Movement Specialist Applicants, Review Process, Albert-Brown, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Movement Specialist Applicants, Review Process, Carson-Cowles, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Movement Specialist Applicants, Review Process, Friede-Jay, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Movement Specialist Applicants, Review Process, Kindon-Ruben, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Movement Specialist Applications, Review Process, Schwartz-Wiener, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Company Applicants, Aman Folk Ensemble, Dances, Review Process, Janet-Soares, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Company Applicants, Review Process, Paschal Guzman/Downtown Ballet-Claude Kipinis Mime Theater, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Company Applicants, Review Process, Ko-Thi Dance Company-Mordine and Company, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Dance Company Applicants, Review Process, Edith Stephen Dance Connection-Maruja Vargas Compania del Oro, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Companies, Tandy Beal and Company-Magic Movers, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Companies, Morca-Flamenco in Concert, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Companies, One Plus One-Sounds in Motion, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Movement Specialists, Bell-Chizik, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Movement Specialists, Coleman-Erkert, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Movement Specialists, Hruby-Kaemmerlin, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Movement Specialists, Kaller-MacLane, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Movement Specialists, Martin-Nelson, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Movement Specialists, Nelson-Sherman, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Project Management, Artists in Schools, Review Panel Book I (All Applicants), Dance Movement Specialists, Wilson-Zyznar (Box 24)
  - Michigan, 1975-1976 (Box 24)
  - Michigan, 1975-1976 (Box 24)
  - New Hampshire-Virgin Islands, Correspondence and Contact Information (Box 25)
  - Alabama-Michigan, Correspondence and Contact Information (Box 25)
  - Minnesota, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Missouri, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Nevada, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - New Hampshire, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - New Jersey, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - New Mexico, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - New Mexico ESAA, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - New York, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - North Carolina, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - North Dakota, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Ohio, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Oklahoma, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Oregon, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Pennsylvania, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Puerto Rico, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Rhode Island, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - South Dakota (Box 25)
  - Tennessee, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Texas, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Texas, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - SAA AIS Grant Applications, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
  - NEA AIS State Applications with Notes, Panel Action Aug. 24-26, 1977, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
  - AIS/DC NEA State Grant Letters, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
  - SAA Grant Letter from Endowment, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
  - Ballet de San Juan, Areyto (Box 26)
  - Ririe-Woodbury Dance Company (Box 26)
  - Atlanta Contemporary Dance Company (Box 26)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem (Box 26)
  - Dances We Dance (Box 26)
  - Hawaiian Dance Companies (Box 26)
  - Nancy Hauser Dance Company (Box 26)
  - Arthur Hall's Afro-American Dance Company (Box 26)
  - AIS Companies, General Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Regional Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Regional Meetings, Title III, Apr. 1972 (Box 26)
  - AIS Regional Meetings, Meeting Sched., Agenda, Sites, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Regional Meetings, Follow-Up Letters, Reports, Thank you's, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Regional Workshops, Transportation, Hotel Reimbursement, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Regional Workshop, Participants, August, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Workshop, July 27-29, 1972, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Summer Workshop Notes, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - AIS Workshop, Group Leaders Notes, 1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Workshop Agenda, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - Regional Meetings Agenda, Meeting Sites, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - Regional Meetings Participants, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - Regional Meetings, Invitations, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - Regionals, Larry Greene (Box 26)
  - Regional Meetings, Thank you's from Participants, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - Regional Meetings, Hotels, Travel Information, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - AIS Regional Meeting Reimbursement, Aug. 27-31, 1973 (Box 26)
  - AIS Workshop Housing, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - AIS/DC Workshop Room Information Forms, 1976-1977 (Box 26)
  - AIS Workshop, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - AIS Workshop, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
  - Oregon Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - Pennsylvania, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Pennsylvania Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - Puerto Rico, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Puerto Rico Phone Cals (Box 27)
  - Rhode Island, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Rhode Island Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - Tennessee Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - Tennessee, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Texas, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Texas Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - Utah, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Utah Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - Virgin Islands, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Virgin Islands Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - Washington, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Washington Phone Calls (Box 27)
  - AIS/Dance Component Wisconsin, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Non-Participating States, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - State Forms, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - DMS Assistant's Resumes, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Residency Information Sheets, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - AIS/Dance Component Log Sheets, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Ann Brunsvik Brown (Box 27)
  - Leslie Cerier (Box 27)
  - Elinor Coleman (Box 27)
  - Linda Diamond (Box 27)
  - Abby Fiat (Box 27)
  - Elsa E. Fletcher (Box 27)
  - Frances Flint (Box 27)
  - Marysue Garlinger (Box 27)
  - Darlene Handler (Box 27)
  - Robin Edward Johnson (Box 27)
  - Lanie Keystone (Box 27)
  - Maria Jimena Lasansky (Box 27)
  - Richard Alan Levi (Box 27)
  - Carol M. Loud (Box 27)
  - Maggie MacGowan (Box 27)
  - Elsa Posey Novak (Box 27)
  - Barbara Pearson (Box 27)
  - Peggy Schwartz (Box 27)
  - Andrea Sherman (Box 27)
  - Judith M. Stames (Box 27)
  - Vicki Stern (Box 27)
  - Anna Tilton (Box 27)
  - Lynn Walter Topovski (Box 27)
  - Maureen P. Williams (Box 27)
  - Pauline Koner Dance Consort (Box 27)
  - New Mexico Dance Works Inc. (Box 27)
  - Alvin Ailey Repertory Ensemble (Box 27)
  - Nancy Hauser Dance Company (Box 27)
  - Review Process, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Review Process, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Missouri, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Nevada, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - New York, ESAA, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - North Carolina, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - North Dakota, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Oklahoma, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Oregon, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Pennsylvania, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Puerto Rico, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Tennessee, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Texas, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Washington, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Dance Movement Specialist and Company Statements, 1976-1977 (Box 28)
  - AIS Dance Movement Specialist Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
  - AIS Dance Company Resumes, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
  - Info on Dance Movement Specialists, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
  - AIS Dance Company Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
  - AIS/DC Dance Company Resumes, 1978-1979 (Box 28)
  - AIS Dance Company Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 28)
  - Dance Movement Specialist Statements, AIS/Dance Component, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Dance Company Statements, AIS/Dance Component, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - Agreement for Dance Movement Spec., Self-Employed Contractors, 1978 (Box 28)
  - AIS Statements, Dance Movement Specialists, 1978-1979 (Box 28)
  - Company Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
  - AIS Panel Meeting Dec. 6-9, 1978, Summary of SAA Applications, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
  - AIS SAA Applications, AIS Panel Meeting, Dec. 6-9, 1978 (Box 28)
  - Puerto Rico Reports (Box 28)
  - AIS Panel Meeting, NEA, Dec. 12-14, 1979 (Box 28)
  - AIS Panel Meeting, Jan. 18,19,20, 1978 (Box 28)
  - AIS Advisory Panel, Miscellaneous Corres/Notes (Box 28)
  - AIS Panel Information, Jan. 18-20, 1978 (Box 28)
  - NEA AIS Panel Meeting, Notes, Aug. 24-26, 1977 (Box 28)
  - AIS Panel Meetings, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Dance Panel Mtg., Oct. 2-5, 1977 (Box 28)
  - AIS Advisory Panel Materials, Aug. 24-26, 1977 (Box 28)
  - AIS National Council Meeting, Nov. 1976 (Box 28)
  - AIS Panel Meeting, Dec. 6-8, 1978 (Box 28)
  - AIS Panel Meeting, June 25-26, 1979 (Box 28)
  - NEA AIS Advisory Panel Meeting, Jan. 1976 (Box 28)
  - NEA AIS Advisory Panel Meeting, Jan. 1976 (Box 28)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Preliminary Suggestions and Draft, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Original, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Correspondence/Mailings, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - AIS Program Information Copies, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - AIS Program Information Office Copies, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - Program Guidelines, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Program Information Originals, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Printing Information, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Correspondence Mailings, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
  - AIS Program Information Office Copies, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
  - AIS Program Information Office Copies, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information and Directory, Printing Information, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Correspondence/Mailings, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information, Final Draft to NEA, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Original, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information and Directory, Printing Information, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Original, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS Program Information Office Copies, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information Draft and Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Program Information and Directory, Printing Information, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - AIS Program Information Office Copies, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - AIS Directory, Office Copies, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - AIS Directory Originals, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory Originals, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - AIS Directory Office Copies, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory Correspondence/Mailings, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory Office Copies, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Memos Sent With Prog. Info. And Direct., 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - AIS Program Information File Copies, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - AIS/Dance Component Program Information, Originals, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - Program Information, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - AIS Directory Originals, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory Correspondence/Mailings, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory, Instruction/Forms to Artists, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory, Notes/Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS Directory Office Copies, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS Directory Originals, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory, Instructions/Forms to Artists, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - AIS/DC Directory, Instructions/Forms to Artists, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - ADF Coordinator's Workshop 1977, June 25, 1977-July 1, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Drafts of Memo (Box 29)
  - Memo, Nov. 6, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Memo, Nov. 7, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Memo, Nov. 8, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Chicago: Memo, Nov. 17, 1977 (Box 29)
  - San Francisco, Nov. 18, 1977 (Box 29)
  - DTP Meetings, Fall, 1977 (Box 29)
  - DTP Companies Mailing List, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - DTP Meeting Expenses, Fall, 1977 (Box 29)
  - DTP Attendance Reports, Nov. 1977 (Box 29)
  - "Role Of The Union" DTP Meetings, Nov. 6, 1977 (Box 29)
  - June Arey Materials, DTP/CRTP Origins (Box 29)
  - Regional Organizations, Correspondence (Box 29)
  - Branch Survey Summary (Box 29)
  - DTP/General (Box 29)
  - DTP Report, 1967-1974, Fall 1975 (Box 29)
  - DTP C.C.'s/ Dance Pgm. Memos (Box 29)
  - DTP C.C.'s/ Dance Pgm. Memos (Box 29)
  - Dance Touring Program (Box 30)
  - DTP Questionnaire Slush File (Box 30)
  - DTP Questionnaire (final copy) (Box 30)
  - Dance Touring Program Survey (Box 30)
  - DTP, 1977-1979 (Box 30)
  - DTP Handbook (Box 30)
  - DTP Handbook (Box 30)
  - CRTP Sample Company Contract (Box 30)
  - DTP/Tech Assistant (Box 30)
  - DTP Directory Conference DC, 1974-1975 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 30)
  - CRMI Gen Correspondence, 1966-1979 (Box 30)
  - CRMI General, 1970 (Box 30)
  - CRMI General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 30)
  - Professional Fee's, Mar. 1976- Feb. 1978 (Box 30)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 30)
  - Continental (Box 30)
  - Loans (Box 30)
  - Entertainment and Gifts, 1972-1978 (Box 30)
  - Don, Party, Nov. 18, 1974 (Box 30)
  - Employee Benefits, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
  - Party For Susan Hunter, Dec. 6, 1975 (Box 30)
  - Johnson Dance Theatre, Kafri, Kulkarni, Kamin, Les Grands Ballets Canadiens, Lister Dance Company, Malavika, McGehee, McLean (The Winter Dances), Pardo, Perras, Phakavali, Rafael and Juliana, Ramin (Box 30)
  - Johnson Dance Theatre, Kafri, Kulkarni, Kamin, Les Grands Ballets Canadiens, Lister Dance Company, Malavika, McGehee, McLean (The Winter Dances), Pardo, Perras, Phakavali, Rafael and Juliana, Ramin (Box 30)
  - Rebecca, A Dance Mime Concert, Ridgeway, Ruiz, Somer, The Afro Haitian Folkloric Troup, Vargas, Vesak-Dance and The Symphony, Vetra, Wilson and Company, Wu (Box 31)
  - Barrault, Bashkar, Beers, Benhamin, Brelsfoard, Clouser, Confetti Dance Theatre Inc., Condodina and Dance Company, Contreras Dance Company, Comedy In Dance-Cynthia Fisk and Mara Bowlin, Destine, Electric Symphony Orchestra, Hakoshima, Anna Marie and David Holmes (Box 31)
  - ACUCM (Box 31)
  - ACUCM (Box 31)
  - ACUCM (Box 31)
  - Affiliate Artists (Box 31)
  - Cartoons by Alec, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Alliance Of Western Colleges (Box 31)
  - American Dance Machine (Box 31)
  - American Folk Ballet (Box 31)
  - Ballet Rambert (Box 31)
  - Bennett, Isadora (Box 31)
  - Taylor-Edinburgh Clippings, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Reviews From Edinburgh Festival and Holland Festival, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Virginia (Box 31)
  - Additional Schools (Box 31)
  - Goldwyn-Press Clippings (Box 31)
  - Alba/Reyes, Stage Info (Box 31)
  - A/R Reviews (Box 31)
  - A/R Clippings (Box 31)
  - Fitz Maurice (Box 31)
  - A/R Old (X-V) (Box 31)
  - Tunisia Clippings, 1966 (Box 31)
  - Nikolais (Box 31)
  - Sokolow (Box 31)
  - Anna Halprin (Box 31)
  - The Young Lovers (Motion Picture), 1964 (Box 31)
  - Cunningham (Box 31)
  - Cunningham (Box 31)
  - Master List and Agenda, List of Arrivals in Detroit (Box 32)
  - Goldwyn Misc Corr (Box 32)
  - Goldwyn (Box 32)
  - For Meeting, Sept. 15, 1964 (Box 32)
  - Alba Reyes, 1964-1965 (Box 32)
  - A/R Contracts (Box 32)
  - Alba/Reyes, 1965-1966 (Box 32)
  - Maria Alba-Ramon de los Reyes, Press Clippings, Publicity, Program Copy, Etc. (Box 32)
  - Student Representatives by Division (Box 32)
  - A/R Accounting (Box 32)
  - The Young Lovers (Motion Picture), 1964 (Box 32)
  - Biographies of Dancers (Box 32)
  - Income and Bills, Lucas Hoving (Box 32)
  - Bio's, Reviews, Etc, Lucas Hoving (Box 32)
  - Reviews, Lucas Hoving Co. (Box 32)
  - Tech Reviews, Etc, Hoving Co. (Box 32)
  - Donald McKayle Co. (Box 32)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co., 1967 (Box 32)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co. Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Taylor Broadway Clippings, 1966 (Box 32)
  - Taylor, USA 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
  - Taylor, USA, Fall, 1967 (Box 32)
  - Taylor Vs. PBL (Box 32)
  - Review of Taylor Co., 1968 (Box 32)
  - Taylor Tu and Films (Box 32)
  - Reinhart Management/Paul Taylor Co., 1967 (Box 32)
  - Glen Tetley Dance Co., Programs, Bios, Etc. (Box 32)
  - Taylor and Co., Trip to New Delhi, 1967 (Box 32)
  - Glen Tetley Dance Co., Mary Hinkson and Scott Douglas, 1967-1972 (Box 32)
  - ADF, 1967-1978 (Box 32)
  - ADF, 1967-1978 (Box 32)
  - Kinney Rent A Car Corp, Company Credit Application, Feb. 1970 (Box 33)
  - NY State Council on Arts Application (Box 33)
  - NY State Council on the Arts (Box 33)
  - NY State Fashion Institute Of Technology (Box 33)
  - NY State Council on the Arts, 1969 (Box 33)
  - NY State Touring Program, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
  - NY State Don Redlich, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
  - Monk, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
  - NY State McKayle, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
  - Paul Taylor, Festival Of Two Worlds, Spoleto, Italy, 1964 (Box 33)
  - Paris, 1966 (Box 33)
  - S. Dept. Background, South America, Printed (Box 33)
  - SA Europe Tour, Accounting, 1965 (Box 33)
  - State Department, Paul Taylor, 1965 (Box 33)
  - PT. Paris (Box 33)
  - London, 1964 (Box 33)
  - Contracts, Paul Taylor, S.A. and Europe, 1965 (Box 33)
  - Holland and Koln, 1965 (Box 33)
  - P.T. Tour Accounts, Paris and London (Box 33)
  - Paul Taylor Newsclippings, 1964 (Box 33)
  - P.T. Foreign Berlin, 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Paul Taylor Clippings and Press Release, 1963-1965 (Box 33)
  - Broadway, 1965 (Box 33)
  - Contracts, Chicago (Box 33)
  - Chicago Festival, 1965 (Box 33)
  - Chicago Festival, 1966 (Box 33)
  - Long Island Festival (Box 33)
  - Long Island Festival, 1965 (Box 33)
  - Long Island Festival, 1964 (Box 33)
  - Nassau County Festival (Box 33)
  - Nassau County Festival (Box 33)
  - Billy Rose Clips (Box 34)
  - Dance Press Lists (Box 34)
  - Billy Rose Theatre, Box Office Statements, 1969 (Box 34)
  - Dance Ad Copies (Box 34)
  - Billy Rose Theatre, Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, Program, 1969 (Box 34)
  - Correspondence (Box 34)
  - Pembroke College Arts Festival, Oct. 7-9, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor, Airgram, Nov. 1965 (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor, Playbill, Press, 1967-1969 (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Brazil, Newspaper Clippings, June 1965 (Box 34)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 34)
  - International Festival Programs, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Programs from Paul Taylor Appearances, 1966-1968 (Box 34)
  - ADF Program, 1967 (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor Newspaper Clippings, 1965 (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor Newspaper Clippings, Sau Paulo, 1965 (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor Reviews, Spoleto, Italy, 1964 (Box 34)
  - Harkness Ballet Ticket Order Form (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor Press, 1965 (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor Clippings (2) (Box 34)
  - Paul Taylor Clippings (Box 34)
  - Reinhart and Upton Correspondence Letters, 1967 (Box 34)
  - Monk, Correspondence Letter, Alfred University, 1969 (Box 34)
  - Ailey, Alvin, Correspondence Letter, Limestone College, Nov. 3, 1971 (Box 34)
  - McKayle, Letter, Aug. 11, 1968 (Box 34)
  - Paid Bills, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Tomkins County Center For Culture And The Performing Arts, Inc., Correspondence, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Management Training Program (Box 34)
  - Lucas Hoving, General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 34)
  - Lucas Hoving (Box 34)
  - Lucas Hoving, 1968-1969 (Box 34)
  - Lucas Hoving, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
  - Lucas Hoving, 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - Lucas Hoving, 1967-1968 (Box 34)
  - National Dance Foundation (Box 35)
  - NDF Budgets (Box 35)
  - NDF Releases, Publicity (Box 35)
  - Association Of American Dance Companies (Box 35)
  - Association Of American Dance Companies (Box 35)
  - Paper Bag Players (Box 35)
  - Robert Joffrey Ballet (Box 35)
  - Ravi Shankar (Box 35)
  - Antonio Gades (Box 35)
  - Pennsylvania Ballet Company, 1966-1967 (Box 35)
  - Antonio Gades Newspaper Clippings, 1966 (Box 35)
  - Continental Concerto Contracts, 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Asia and Asian Contracts (Box 35)
  - Antonio Gades (Box 35)
  - Ximenez-Vargas, Ballet Espanol (Box 35)
  - Performing Arts Management, David and Anna Marie Holmes (possible clients), circa 1960 (Box 35)
  - Performing Arts Management, Soloists of Rio, 1965-1966 (Box 35)
  - Somer, Press Releases and Clippings (Box 35)
  - Somer, Piano Technique (Box 35)
  - Somer, Romania (Box 35)
  - Somer (Box 35)
  - Hilde Somer (Box 35)
  - Archer and Gile (Box 35)
  - Redlich Income (Box 35)
  - Don Redlich Dance Company, Programs, Reviews, 1966-1970 (Box 35)
  - Redlich, Reviews and Bios (Box 35)
  - Redlich, Reviews and Bios (Box 35)
  - Performing Arts Management, Printing Plate no. 6, Promotional Brochure, Glen Tetley and Company, circa 1964 (Box 36)
  - Performing Arts Management, Printing Plates 3, 4, 5, Lucas Hoving; Paul Taylor Dance Company; Paul Taylor Dance Company (couple image), circa 1964 (Box 36)
  - Performing Arts Management, Printing Plate no. 2, Promotional Brochure, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Orbs, circa 1964 (Box 36)
  - Performing Arts Management, Printing Plate no. 1, Promotional Brochure, Paul Taylor Dance Co.; Alba/Reyes; Nala Najan (Box 36)
  - Performing Arts Management, Printing Plate no. 1, Promotional Brochure, Paul Taylor Dance Co.; Alba/Reyes; Nala Najan (Box 36)
  - Redlich, General (Box 37)
  - Shanta Rao (Box 37)
  - Chitrasena and Vajira (Box 37)
  - Daniel Nagrin (Box 37)
  - Don Redlich, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
  - Don Redlich, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
  - Don Redlich, 1968-1969 (Box 37)
  - Don Redlich, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
  - DMS and Dance Co. Applicants, Reviewed for 1976 Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 37)
  - Mini-Panel Meeting, Aug. 4, 1976 (Box 37)
  - Post-Review Process Correspondence for Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 37)
  - Consultants Payment, 1976 (Box 37)
  - All Nations Company, Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - American Folk Ballet, Fall, 1975 (Box 37)
  - Areyto Ballet Folklorico, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Ballet De San Juan, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Fusion Dance Company, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Lotte Goslar's Pantomime Circus, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Hartford Ballet, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Raymond Johnson Dance Company, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Bruce King Dance Concert, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - The Moving Company, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Daniel Nagrin Theatre, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Walter Nicks Dance Theatre Workshop, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Sounds in Motion, Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - South Street Dance Co. (E. Foreman), Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Edith Stephen Dance Co., Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - Teresa Torkanowski Spanish Dance Tht., Applied Fall 1975 (Box 37)
  - NEA Applicant Correspondence, 1976, 1977 for 1978-1979 Directory (Box 37)
  - 1976-1977 Applicant Correspondence for 1978-1979 Directory (Box 37)
  - Interested Applicants for AIS/Dance Co., 1978-1979 Directory, Correspondence in 1976 (Box 37)
  - Back Up for Charles Reinhart at the Dance Panel Meeting for 1978-1979 Directory, 1977 (Box 37)